LUCIMARA MACEDO

JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER



07389 821600



lucimacedom@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/lucimaramacedom



https://github.com/LuciMacedo



Milton Keynes - UK

EDUCATION

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

HyperionDev Current enrolled

IGNITE-REACT COURSE

Rocketseat

Sep - 2022

WEB GAME DEVELOPER

Digital Innovation One May - 2022

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Gama Academy Jun -2021

DEGREE PHYSICAL EDUCATION

Dom Bosco University Dec - 2008

SKILLS

- Python
- Problem-solving
- JavaScript
- Interpersonal Skills
- HTML
- Attention to detail
- CSS
- Self-awareness
- React
- Self-learning
- Git
- Time management
- GitHub

OBJECTIVE

To leverage my knowledge and experience in a dynamic organization that provides robust opportunities for professional growth and development, while utilizing my skills and expertise to contribute to the success of the company.

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

A focused, results-driven, and highly capable Junior Software Engineer offering sound theoretical knowledge and practical experience in projects using Python, JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS, Git, and GitHub. Utilizes superior professional abilities to ensure that users can easily interact with the program. A team player who develops communicative working relationships to ensure the smooth running of daily processes

EXPERIENCE

Please find the selected projects I have developed in my portfolio on the following web links:

- https://www.lucimacedo.com
- https://www.hyperiondev.com/portfolio/146288/

TEACHER ASSISTENT

Walnuts School

March 2023 - Present

Providing individual or small group assistance to students who need extra help or attention.

DEPUTY SITE MANAGER

Fit For Sport

Set 2018 - Nov 2020

I was responsible for managing all aspects of running the club and providing a structured environment for children's growth and development. **Key achievement:** One of my key achievements was reducing customer complaints by implementing a new feature on the booking website. This feature made it easy to identify student classrooms and transport them from their classrooms to session locations. As a result of this new feature, I received positive feedback from parents and the School Principal.

PE TEACHER, SWIMMING TEACHER, AND COORDINATOR

Bom Jesus Educational Group - Brazil

Feb 2008 - Feb 2018 (10 yrs)

My responsibilities included managing employees to deliver a safe and effective program and providing effective communication with parents. **Key achievement:** successfully planned and executed a variety of sports events throughout the year with exceptional attention to detail and a focus on providing memorable experiences for participants.

LANGUAGES

- Portuguese
- English